### **ANDUALEM CHANIE**

#### **COMPUTER ENGINEER**



I am a junior full stack React developer with self-taught skills and internship experience in both front-end and backend development. I graduated in Computer Engineering, achieving a cumulative GPA of 3.51 and a National Exit Examination score of 74%.

☑ azawuntublatena@gmail.com

Addis Ababa

**☐** Date of birth 09/02/2000

096 899 0756

### **General Skills**

#### **Microsoft Office**

Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint.

### **Operating Systems**

Windows and Linux

#### **Version Control**

Git, GitHub

#### **Typing Speed**

50 WPM

# Languages

**Amharic** 

**English** 

### Social networks



@AzawuntuBlatena

## Work experience

Full Stack Developer Intern Fi

From October 2023 to February 2024

### I Tech Company, Addis Ababa

- Contributed to the development of web applications using React for the front-end and Node.js for the back-end.
- Assisted in the integration of RESTful APIs with the front-end interface.
- Collaborated with the development team on code reviews and debugging.
- Gained hands-on experience with version control using Git and deployment with Docker.

**ICT Intern** 

From June 2022 to October 2022

#### Woldiya University, Woldia

My internship experience at Woldia University ICT Directorate provided me with hands-on experience in maintaining electronic devices, installing networks. I was able to successfully solve hardware and software problems, contribute to the repair and utilization of damaged devices.

## **Projects**

Final Year Project: Share Management System

During my final year of studies, I undertook a comprehensive project to develop a Share Management System for a company. The system was developed by a team using Nextjs for the frontend, Nodejs for the backend, and MongoDB for the database. It was designed to digitalize day-to-day operations, including trading shares, managing shareholder information, and keeping track of shareholders and share data.

YouTube Home Page Clone, Frontend

Link: https://azabla-youtube-homepage.netlify.app/

**Ecommerce-Homepage, Frontend** 

link: <a href="https://azabla-ecommerce-homepage.netlify.app/#">https://azabla-ecommerce-homepage.netlify.app/#</a>

Book Library Website : Fullstack(backend)
Link: https://bete-book-1.onrender.com/books

# **Programming Skills**

Front-End:

JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Next.js, Redux, HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap

**Back-End:** 

Node.js, Express.js, SQL, MongoDB, Firebase

# **Education**

**Bachelor Degree** 

From January 2018 to June 2023

Bahirdar University, Bahirdar

**High School and Preparatory** 

From February 2015 to October 2017

Robit Preparatory School,

**Robit**